导演
温子仁（前译“詹姆斯·温”）
主演
帕特里克·威尔森  饰  賈許
你好，我是伊莉丝，您就是罗琳吧？
Hi. I'm Elise.You must be Lorraine.
是的，幸会，实在是不好意思
Yes. Nice to meet you.I'm sorry it's so late.
为了我儿子的事，这么晚打搅您休息了
My day job kind of makes raising my son a night job.
没关系，不打紧的
Don't worry about it.
我平常工作都在夜间
In my line of work, things tend to happen when it gets dark.
-请进吧
-谢谢
-Please.
-Thank you.
亲爱的卡尔！
Ahoy, Carl!
伊莉丝！你能来真是太好了！
Elise, thank you for coming.
我实在是没辙了，只好打电话给你
I didn't know what else to do, except call you.
我明白
Oh, I understand.
这事对你来说很棘手
You had a big problem and you thought
你怕我嫌麻烦是吗？
you'd make it my problem, too.Is that it'?
额，嗯
Uh, uh..
我開玩笑的！
I'm teasing.
你知道我總是樂於助人的，卡尔
You know I'm always happy to help, Carl.
您喝点什么，咖啡还是茶？
Would you like some coffee or tea?
不用了，謝謝
No, thank you.
如果没问题的话，我想马上开始做正事
I'd like to get started right away, if that's okay.
卡尔电话里跟我说
Carl told me on the phone
令郎身体有异常，是吗？
your son is the one affected, is that right?
是的，没错
Yes, that's right.
我儿子，賈許
My son, Josh.
有东西跟着他
Something is following him.
拿给她看
Show her.
我给賈許做了全身常规检查
I started with all the usual checks,
做了心理健康测试，查阅了病历报告
mental health tests,medical records.
一切正常
Everything normal.
直到我看到这些照片
Then I saw the photos.
六周之前首次发现异状
First noticed it about six weeks ago.
起初我们以为是相机破了
Thought it was a camera problem.
但后来发觉事态越发严重
Then it became apparent that it was more than that.
我问过賈許
I interviewed the boy.
他什么都不肯说，他很害怕
He won't tell me anything.He's afraid.
我也很怕
I'm afraid, too.
这屋里一定潜伏着什么，我能感觉到
There's something in this house.I can feel it.
这东西不想让我呆在这
It doesn't want me here.
我要见见賈許
May I meet him?
嗨，賈許，我叫伊莉丝
Hi, Josh. I'm Elise.
我想问你几个简单的问题
I would love to ask you some simple questions.
你喜欢住在这栋房子里吗？
Do you like living here?
恩，还好吧
Yeah, I guess
这附近有和你差不多年纪的小孩吗？
Are there a lot of kids your age in this neighborhood?
有几个，隔壁就有一个
A few.One kid lives next door.
那敢情好
That must be fun.
住在这屋里有没有感觉不舒服的地方？
Is there anything you don't like about living in this house?
我有时会做噩梦
I have bad dreams sometimes.
是什么样的噩梦？
What happens in your dreams?
我们来做一个小试验，賈許
I'd like to try something with you, Josh.
阿姨保证，一点儿都不痛的
And I promise, it won't hurt.
全身放松
I want you to just relax.
听着摆针的声音
Listen to the ticking.
其他什么都不要想
Focus on it.
什么都不用管
Tune everything else out.
你感到好困，你好想睡觉
Feel yourself getting sleepier.
现在，我们进入你的梦境了，賈許
We are now inside your dream, Josh.
看看周围
Look around.
你看到了什么
What do you see?
我看到我自己
I see myself
在床上睡觉
sleeping in bed.
在你的卧室吗
Are you in your bedroom?
不是
No.
在一个黑暗的地方
I'm somewhere dark.
那地方一直都很黑
It's always dark here.
是你一个人吗？
Are you alone?
不
No.
她也在
She's here.
她是谁？
Who is "she"?
她说她是我的朋友
She says she's a friend.
她每天晚上都来看我
She visits me every night.
现在呢，她在哪里？
Where is she right at this moment?
她是不是就在这，我们身边？
Is she here in this house with us?
我想跟她聊聊
I'd like to talk to her.
这样吧，我们来玩个小游戏，賈許
Okay, we're gonna play a little game, Josh.
叫做“冷热自知”
It's called Hot and Cold.
我在屋里到处走
I'll walk around the house,
如果我靠近你的朋友，你就说“我热”；离得远，你就说“我冷”
and you tell me if I'm getting warmer or colder.
我冷
Cold.
我热了
Warm.
我热
Warmer.
冷了
Colder.
我热了
Getting warm.
更热了
Hotter.
我好热
It's very hot.
请你...离开那里
Please get out of there.
你是谁？
Who are you?
你想做什麼？
What do you want?
怎麼了？
What happened?
我看到那家伙了，它绝非善类
I saw what haunts him,and it's not a friend.
是一种寄生灵，我职业生涯从未碰到过此等恶灵
It's a, parasite. I've never felt such a malignant presence.
它想夺取賈許的肉身
It wants to be him.
兰伯特太太
Miss Lambert,
我认为令郎拥有特殊的能力，一种天赋
I think your son has a unique ability a gift.
当他入睡时，他能够元神出窍，星光体投射
When he sleeps at night, he's able to go places, see things.
会看到各种肉眼看不见的灵魂
Things no living person is supposed to see.
而现在，那只寄生灵盯上他了
Only now, one of the dead has seen him, too.
哦...天啊
Oh.. my God.
那，你能阻止它吗？
Well, can you stop it?
我只能暂时封存
I could take away his gift
賈許元神出窍的能力
to suppress his memory of his ability.
如何封存？
How would we do that'?
我带你去
I'll show you.
请你赶快作法，让他忘掉这一切吧
Do whatever you have to make him forget.
片名：《潜伏2》
===百度悬疑片吧字幕组===
水浒三国金刚  非晓生  AS小笼包
林·沙烨   饰   伊莉丝
史蒂夫·考特  饰  卡尔
芭芭拉·赫希  饰  罗琳
“昨天晚上，我看见我自己。。。”
人设原案
雷·沃纳尔（金刚注：本片中饰演斯佩克斯）
故事
温子仁
雷·沃纳尔
编剧
导演
温子仁
一天早上，我们大儿子道爾頓陷入了长久昏迷状态
One morning, Dalton just wouldn't wake up.
我们带他去看能够找到的最好的医生
We took him to the best doctors we could find,
但劳而无功
but none of them had any idea.
最后没办法，只好回到家里
Eventually,we just took him home,
可他仍然昏迷不醒
still in his coma.
之后那房子里，就开始发生各种怪事
Then things started happening around the house.
无法解释的怪象
Unexplained things.
搞得我心烦意乱，不得不搬家
I got so freaked out, we moved.
但还是鬼影缠身
But they kept happening.
所以你相信，有某种超自然的灵魂力量？
And you believe that there was some sort of supernatural force at work?
你们什么时候雇佣那个灵媒师的？
When did you hire the services
也就是死者伊莉丝·蕊妮儿
of the deceased Elise Rainier?
我们，走投无路的时候
When we ran out of places to go.
根据你的口供，兰伯特太太
It says in your statement, Mrs. Lambert,
昨天晚上，确切地说是昨晚10点
that last night, at approximately 10:00 p.m.,
灵媒师伊莉丝对你丈夫实施所谓的“灵媒法事”
Elise put your husband into a state of hypnosis.
她声称你丈夫经过催眠
She did this as part of a ritual that
开始所谓的“星光体投射”
she believed would allow him to
可以令他的元神进入。。。
project his unconscious into a..
额。。不好意思，字写得有点潦草
Uh..I'm sorry, I can't read my own handwriting.
进入灵界“里关世界”，在那他能够救出你们的儿子
..Into a spirit realm, where he could locate your son
并将他带回人间“表关世界”
and bring him back to consciousness.
我说，你真的相信这一切吗？
Now, did you really believe that would help?
我只能相信了，不管伊莉丝做了什么，她确实成功了
I had to. Whatever she did, it worked.
道爾頓苏醒了
Dalton woke up.
然后呢，你儿子醒了以后呢
And what happened after your son woke up?
賈許！
Josh!
賈許你在哪？
Josh, where are you?
賈許！
Josh!
蕾纳依
Renai
我在这
I'm right here.
蕾纳依，怎么了
Renai!What?
哦不不不
Oh, no, no, no.
伊莉丝？伊莉丝！
Elise! Elise!
妈，快带道爾頓离开这，快叫救护车！
Mom, get Dalton out of here!Call an ambulance!
不..不不，伊莉丝？伊莉丝？
No, no, no. Elise!
哦，不！
Oh, no!
不，不会的！
No, no!
干嘛？
What?
干嘛这么看着我？
Why are you looking at me like that?
你认为是我干的？
You think I did this?
你信任他吗？
Did you believe him?
-他是我丈夫
-回答我的问题
-He's my husband.
-That's not what I asked.
是的，我信任他，我丈夫不会杀人的
Yes, I believed him. My husband isn't capable of killing anybody.
这是伊莉丝被杀一瞬间拍到的快照
This is a photo Elise took seconds before she was killed.
你能给我解释一下这张照片吗？
Can you tell me who that is in this picture?
我家里发生过很多怪事
There were a lot of strange things happening in our house.
我看到过各种鬼魂
I saw apparitions,lots of them.
得，你是说照片里的事是鬼干的？
Are you telling me that this is a photograph of a ghost?
可我对鬼没兴趣，兰太太
Listen, I'm not interested in ghosts, Mrs. Lambert.
我关心的是制造这起凶杀案的活人
I'm interested in the living people who create them.
伊莉丝遭锁喉致死
Elise has marks on her neck
抠痕已证实是人类的双手所致
that were put there by human hands.
一旦鉴证科确认抠痕指纹和你丈夫的匹配，我会立刻通知你
I'll let you know if forensics matches those marks to your husband.
杰西卡，我们回来了
Jessica, we're home.
嗨孩子们！
Hey, guys.
-爸爸！给你看样好东西
-嘿！
-Dad! Look what I made.
-Hey.
-是什么？
-罐頭電話筒
-What?
-It's a cup phone.
看到没？耳朵听这头，可以听到那头讲的话
See? You put your ear in that,and I put my mouth in that.
你真是個天才。谢谢你照顾他们
You are a genius.Absolute brilliance.Thanks for watching them.
-代我向令堂问好
-嗯谢谢
-Say hi to your mom from me.
-I will.
妈妈你放着罢，我来拿
Oh. Mom,I'll get that.
我上楼去铺床
I'll go up and make the beds.
好了
All right.
该睡觉了，小帅哥们
Time for bed, boys.
我们要在这呆多久？
How long are we gonna be here for?
还得在奶奶这住上一段日子
We're gonna be at Grandma's house for a little bit
因为警察在检查我们的房子
while the police work at our house.
你知道嗎，这里可是爸爸的老家哦
You know, this house has been in the family for a long time.
你们睡的床
And you guys
就是爸爸小时候睡过的床
get to stay in Daddy's old bedroom.
你小时候在这见过可怕的东西吗？
Did you see anything bad in here?
没有
No.
你也不会的，好吗
And neither will you, okay?
好吧
Okay.
晚安
Good night.
怎么了
What?
你病好了，爸爸很开心
Just glad you're awake.
晚安，孩子们
Good night, boys.
晚安
Good night.
嘿，道爾頓
Hey, Dalton.
干嘛
What?
想不想玩这个
Look what I made.
一定要玩吗？
Do I have to?
是啊
Yeah.
这也太傻了
This is stupid.
来嘛，可好玩了，来，我问你问题
Come on, it really works. I wanna ask you something, all right?
好吧好吧，这绳子应该再紧些
All right, fine. The string needs to be tight.
-後退點
-嗯
-Go farther back.
-Okay.
怎么样，好不好玩
So, what do you think of this?
我觉得傻到爆
I think it's stupid.
嘿
Hey
罗琳？
Lorraine?
放轻松
It's okay.
-阴魂不散！
-怎么了？
-It's still happening.
-What is?
楼下的钢琴自己在弹！
I heard the piano playing by itself downstairs
然后凯丽！她趴在地上哭！
and I found Kali on the floor of her room by her crib!
也许凯丽老早学会一个人爬进爬出了呢？
Well, maybe she climbed out of her crib.
她以前有没有爬出来过？
Has she ever done that before?
甚么？！你究竟是怎么了？！
What? What is wrong with you?
蕾纳依，我只想好好过日子，就这么简单
Renai, I just want us to move on from this, that's all.
我想要回那个正常的家庭
I want us to be a normal family again.
這根本一點都不正常，好嗎 ? 那瘟神还在这！
There is nothing normal about this,okay?
These things are still here！
伊莉丝是怎么死的！打开天窗说亮话吧：她是被人杀害的！
Elise is dead! No one's talking about it!
Someone murdered her!
话都说到这份上了
Then let's talk about it.
你意思她是我杀的？
You think I did it?
不是！不，我不是这个意思
No. No, I don't.
好，很好
Good. Good.
因为我知道是怎么一回事
Because I know what happened.
我进入那鬼地方把我们的儿子救回来
I went into that place to get our son back
某个恶魔跟着我出来，杀了伊莉丝
and something evil followed me and killed Elise.
你看到的
You saw it.
这一切你都亲眼看到的
You saw those things.
听我说，我们不会被打扰了，再也不会了
Listen to me. Nothing is gonna bother us, not anymore.
我们一家团聚了
We have our family back.
儿子没事了
We have our son.
这才是重点，不是吗？
Isn't that what we should be focusing on?
没错
Yeah.
尽管咱俩阅鬼无数
You think all the ghosts we've seen
但这并不能缓解我对伊莉丝的伤感
would somehow make me feel better that Elise is gone.
我是说，你我都确信
I mean, you and I have
灵魂可以游走在表里两界
firsthand knowledge that there's something out there beyond death.
可有什么用呢？
But it's not helping.
別人的生活總是比較好的
Turns out the living version of someone is always better.
她从不忘记锁阅览室的门的
She never left the reading room unlocked.
你走前头
You first.
猜拳决定谁先走
Hunter, ninja, bear.
猎人！忍者！熊！
臭狗熊
That's bullshit.
我堂堂忍者怎么会打不过熊呢？
How does a bear beat a goddamn ninja?
熊的鼻子很灵敏的，朋友.
Superior sense of smell, my friend.
我觉得这下面不会有什么线索
You know what'? I don't think we should be down here.
回去吧
Let's go back.
-有间暗房
-你應該待在...
-That's a private room.
-You should stay..
你看道了嗎? 哦我的蛋蛋!
See?Oh, my nuts!
白费力气
I'm not helping.
“賈許·兰伯特（1986）”
“你好，賈許，我叫伊莉丝”
Hi, Josh. I'm Elise.
“你好”
Hey.
“我想问你几个简单的问题”
I would love to ask you some simple questions.
“但关于这些问题，我希望你能如实地回答”
But they're the good kind,the kind you can't get wrong.
“你喜欢住在这里吗？”
Do you like living here?
“喜欢”
Yeah.
一般的影片，只是恐怖了點
Amateur framing.Just horrible.
“有几个。隔壁就有一个”
A few.One kid lives next door.
“你能阻止它吗？”
Can you stop it?
“我只能消除賈許”
I could try to take away his gift
“元神出窍的能力”
to suppress his memory of his ability.
“如何消除？”
How would we do that?
“我带你去”
I'll show you
他在跟谁说话？
Who the hell's he talking to?
“我只能消除賈許”
I could try to take away his gift,
“元神出窍的能力”
to suppress his memory of his ability.
“如何消除？”
How would we do that?
“我带你去”
I'll show you
就在那
Right there.
离她远点
Leave her alone
睡吧，我走
Sleep.Then I flew away.
不要再离开我们了
Please don't leave us again.
奶奶
Grandma?
嗯哼？
Mmm-hmm.
有个人站在你后面
There's someone standing behind you.
蕾纳依？
Renai?
-哎哟我的天哪！賈許！
-妈妈！
-Oh, my God, Josh!
-Mom!
你看见没？我刚才看到有一个人！
Did you see her?I saw someone!
-不，你看错了
-是真的！我亲眼看到的！
-No. you didn't.
-No. I did!!There was somebody..
妈，根本没有什么人
Ma, there is no one here, okay?
因为如果真有人，蕾纳依和孩子们会吓坏的
Because if there was,that would scare my family
我不想再让蕾纳依担惊受怕了
and I don't need Renai hearing any of that stuff right now.
您明白吗？
Understand?
好吧，你说的对，额。。。
Yeah, you're right.Um..
也许是我的幻觉
It was probably my imagination.
恩
Yeah.
好啦，早点休息吧
Sorry. You should get some sleep.
再玩一次？
You want some more?
好了，走远一点，线拉长一点
All right, go farther back so we can stretch it.
把线拉直
We need to make it tight.
爸爸？
Daddy?
-抓到你了！抓到你了！
-不会吧！
-I gotcha! I gotcha!
-Oh, my God!
我要吃了你！
I'm going to eat you.
妈妈
Mom?
宝贝，妈妈给你做早饭
Hey, honey, what do you want for breakfast?
想吃什么？
Anything you want.
隨便
I don't care.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
出了什么事？告诉妈妈
What's the matter?You can tell me.
我做了个噩梦
I had a bad dream.
这样啊
Okay.
好吧，那你梦见什么了？
I'm sorry.What was it about?
我梦见我睡在床上
I was in my bed sleeping.
奶奶走过来
Grandma walked in.
我看见屋里还有另一个人
I could see someone else in my room.
不要再离开我们了
Please don't leave us again.
奶奶
Grandma?
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
有个人站在你后面
There's someone standing behind you.
我很想醒过来
I tried to wake myself up.
但费了好大劲才起床
It took a while, but I did it.
我听见客厅有动静
I heard voices in the hallway.
你必须离开！
You got to go.
你走！
You have to go.
是爸爸
It was Daddy.
马上离开！
You have to leave.
他在跟什么人说话
And he was talking to someone.
走啊！
You have to go.
妈妈，爸爸是不是着魔了
Is there something wrong with Daddy, Mom?
不
No.
不是的宝贝
No, honey.
他只是太累了
He's just been through a lot.
就是这样，大家都太累了
That's all.We all have.
好了，只是个梦罢了
It's okay, it's just a dream.
我送孩子们去上学
I'm gonna take the boys to school.
你再躺会吧，休息一下
You should rest, relax a bit.
走吧，儿子
Come on, son.
去吧
Okay.
罗琳你还好吧？
Are you okay, Lorraine?
你电话里说有古怪？
You said something was wrong.
我不清楚伊莉丝是怎么死的
Whatever it was that killed Elise,
我也不清楚究竟出了什么事，反正我觉得
whatever it was that was haunting my family
我们家又闹鬼了
is not done with us.
昨晚，我在屋里看到一个怪人
Last night I saw someone in my house.
我需要你们的帮助
I need your help.
你还记得伊莉丝第一次去你家的事吗？
Do you remember the first time Elise visited your house
为了賈許的事，那时候賈許还小
to talk to Josh when he was a boy?
我，这么多年来我一直
No. I did a lot to try to..
试图忘掉这件事，可如今。。。
Try to forget that part of my life, until recently.
这是那天晚上伊莉丝拍的灵媒录像带
All right. Well,Elise hypnotized him,
当时伊莉丝问了賈許几个问题
asked him a series of questions.
我数字修复了这盘录像带，提高了亮度
I digitized the actual footage taken from the night.
我剪了这张出来并放大加亮
I cropped and lightened the image.
怎么？！
What?!
罗琳，这个人是賈許吗？
Lorraine, is that Josh?
这怎么可能？！
How is that possible?
我们也搞不懂
We don't know.
要是伊莉丝还在就能帮我们了。。。
If only Elise were here to help us.
怎么了？
What?
喂？
Hello?
蕾纳依·兰伯特太太，我是圣代警官
Renai Lambert,this is Detective Sendai.
哦
Oh.
你好，警官
Hello, Detective.
上次我说过鉴证科验尸报告一出就打给你
I told you I would inform you once I got the forensics results
现在有了一些结果
Well, I got some.
初步判定伊莉丝·蕊妮儿脖子上的抠痕指纹
It seems the bruises on Elise Rainier's neck
与你丈夫的指纹不吻合
do not match your husband's hands
我们警方尚未排除疑点
We're not ruling anything out at this point,
我打过来是想通知你一声
but I just thought you should know.
谢谢你，警官，额。。。
Thank you. Detective.Uh..
我一直都盼着这个结果，太感谢了
I really needed to hear that.Thank you.
划啊划，划大船，荡起我们的双桨
Row, row, row your boat
轻轻进入你梦乡
Gently down the stream
好开森，好快乐，好高兴，好欢畅
Merrily,merrily, merrily, merrily
生活就是梦一场
Life is but a dream
凯丽？
Kali?
凯丽！
凯丽！你在哪！
Kali, what's wrong?
凯丽！凯丽！
Kali! Kali!
多可爱的乖孩子啊
What a beautiful little girl.
你好大胆！
Don't you dare!
天啊！
Jesus!
哦我的天啊！我的天啊！
Oh, my God.Oh, my God!
凯丽！
Kali!
凯丽！宝贝
Kali? Baby?
我的宝贝。。。凯丽。。。
My baby, Kali. Kali.
你好大的膽子！！！
Don't you dare!
他来了
He's here.
卡尔？我叫斯佩克斯，我是打你电话那人
Carl, I'm Specs. I'm the guy you spoke to on the phone.
-哦你好啊
-进来吧
-Oh, hello!
-Come in.
-嗨卡尔
-哦
-Hi, Carl.
-Oh.
好久不见
It's been a long time.
久违了
Yeah.
看起来咱俩只有我一个人变老
Looks like I did the aging for the both of us.
快别这么说
Oh, please stop it.
斯佩克斯你已经认识了，这位是塔克
You met Specs.This is Tucker.
伊莉丝老提您的大名
Elise talked about you a lot.
久仰久仰，她说您是天下
Oh, Yeah, said you were the second best person
第二大灵媒师
She ever worked with.
天下第二？我受寵若驚啊
Second best, that's generous.
我一直想联系她
I had been meaning to catch up with her, to call her.
可总因为有事耽搁
But I always kept putting it off till the next week, you know?
而现在，她却不在了
And now she's gone.
也许今天能给你一个和她道别的机会
Well, maybe this is your chance to say your good-byes.
斯佩克斯在电话里跟我说你们请我来是要。。。？
Specs told me on the phone,but I'm not sure we should..
我们有很多疑问想知道答案
We have questions that need answering,
唯一能解答这些问题的人是伊莉丝
and the only person we could think of to ask is Elise.
请你帮助我们，卡尔
Please help us, Carl.
帮我们与她取得联系
Help us contact her.
不同的灵媒师与里关世界联络有各自不同的方法
Everybody has their own way of making contact.
這是我的方法
This is mine.
先问问题，再掷骰子，灵魂会通过骰子回答
I ask questions and the spirits answer with the dice.
掷出的骰子中将会出现构成答案的字母组合
You look for the words in the letters.
伊莉丝，我们呼唤你
Elise, we are calling out to you.
告诉我们你在不在这
Tell us if you are there.
伊莉丝，请回答
Elise, please talk to us.
提示我们你听见呼唤了
Give us a sign that you can hear my voice.
好吧，我得解释一下
All right, I suppose I should've explained
这种方法是看几率的
that this isn't an exact science.
有时候确实无法连接里关世界
Sometimes contact can't be made.
伊莉丝
Elise.
请你告诉我，你在这里吗？
Please tell me, are you here?
你在不在这？
Are you here?
-我去开灯
-别动！
-I'll go get..
-No!
不要破坏结界
Do not break the circle.
“Y，E，S”
伊莉丝
Elise.
我们想知道是谁杀了你
We need to know who killed you.
告诉我们
Tell us.
“是，她”
她要干嘛？
What does she want?
有了
I see it.
哪里
Where?
“她，要，杀，人”
她在哪？
Where is she?
潜伏
Hiding
她潜伏在哪？
Where is she hiding?
伊莉丝，告诉我们在哪能找到凶手？
Elise, tell us where lo find your killer.
我们的安格力斯小姐？
"Our Lady Angls"?
安格力斯小姐是哪路神仙？
Our Lady Angls,what does that mean?
是“天使”
It's "Angels."
圣母天使
Our Lady of the Angels.
是一家医院的名字
It's a hospital.
我曾经在那上班
I know because I used to work there.
蕾纳依？
Renai?
蕾纳依
Renai.
我大部分工作时间在这医院东区
Most of my work was in this East Wing.
现在这地方完全废弃了
But it's all closed now.
只剩下孤魂野鬼了
Now only the ghosts are left.
如今这世道，人比鬼更可怕
Personally, I prefer the ghosts to people.
问题是，我们到底要找什么？
The question is,what are we looking for?
伊莉丝指示我们来这一定有原因的
Elise led us here for a reason.
别再想地点了
Just forget the actual building.
想想和你共事过的医生，护士
Think of the doctors,the nurses you worked with,
还有病人，所有人
the patients, everyone.
妈妈！妈妈！
Mama! Mama!
怎么了？
What is it?
在那里面
In there.
这间房是用来干嘛的？
What was in this room?
这是重症加护病房（ICU）
This was an ICU.
我记得很清楚
I remember it very well.
晚上我们做披萨吧？
Should we do pizza night tonight?
奶酪通心粉怎么样？
How about mac and cheese?
-嗨帕姆
-嗨罗琳
-Hi, Pam.
-Hi, Lorraine.
奶酪通心粉
Mac and cheese.
好，就这么说定了
Okay, that can be done.
保持安静，不要乱碰
Keep quiet.Don't touch anything.
他怎么样
How is he?
生命体征稳定
His vital signs are stabilizing
但反应还是很迟钝
but he's still unresponsive.
血压好多了
His blood pressure's doing better.
是啊，加了剂量之后
Yes, after we upped the dosage.
- 好的，那就维持计划
- 好
- Okay, let's keep him on that.
- Okay.
上一次检查血糖是什么时候？
And when was the last time you checked the glucose?
没事了，没事的
It's okay.It's okay.
几天后，我又遇到他
A few days later, I saw him again.
那是最后一次见到他
For the last time.
帕克？你怎么。。。
Parker, what are you..
你应该休息啊，你不该下床的
You should be resting.You shouldn't be out of bed.
那天我儿子的事我向你道歉
Listen, I wanna apologize for my son the other day.
小孩子调皮不懂事
He was being a nosy kid.
嘿，希拉里，为什么让104房的病人
Hey, Hillary, why is the patient from Room 104
随意走动？
up and walking around?
你说什么？
What do you mean?
ICU病房的病人帕克·柯蓝
The patient from ICU,Parker Crane?
“随意走动”是什么意思？
What do you mean,walking around?
刚才在电梯里我碰见他了
I just rode down in the elevator with him.
他为什么要放弃治疗啊？
He should be in bed,on the monitor..
罗琳，那位病人昨天早上去世了
Lorraine, that patient died yesterday morning.
什么？！
What?!
他跳楼自杀了
He jumped to his death.
他得什么病住院的？
So, why was he here in the first place?
他试图閹掉自己
He tried to castrate himself.
不，妈的
Oh, no.
别
No.
不，还不到时候
No, not yet.
求你不要
Please, no.
你的死灵正在侵蚀他的肉身
Your dead soul is killing his living skin.
我想活下去
I wanna live.
我想好好过日子！
I wanna live!
除非杀了她们！
Only if you kill them.
不，求你了，不要
No. Please, no.
我做不到，妈妈
I can't, Mother.
求你别再逼我了
Please don't make me do it.
你必须做！
You must!
否则你会日益衰弱！
Or you'll waste away.
找到了！
Yes, we can.
-真的？
-罗琳！
-No way.
-Lorraine!
就是这个人吗？
Is that our man?
帕克·柯蓝，是他！
Parker Crane, that's him.
这个地址，那里一定有事发生
This address,there's something there.
蕾纳依！没事了！蕾纳依！
It's okay, it's okay.Renai.
好了，好了，没事了，我在这
It's okay. It's okay.You're okay. You're okay.
-天哪
-不要慌
-Oh, God.
-You're okay.
凯丽在哪？
Where's Kali?
她没事，她在楼上睡觉
She's fine.She's in her room sleeping.
-她没事
-不，她不见了！不见了！
-She's fine.
-No, she's not!No, she's not!
-她在睡觉！蕾纳依！
-不！不！
-She's asleep! Renai!
-No! No!
凯丽！
Kali.
你看！我说了她没事的
See! I told you，she's fine.
-哦天！
-出什么事了？告诉我
-Oh, God!
-What happened? Tell me.
有人把我打晕了
Someone attacked me!
是谁？
Who?
在卧室，是一个女人，她打我！这屋又闹鬼了！賈許！
In the living room, a woman. She hit me.These things are back, Josh!
我们快走，赶紧带孩子离开这！
We have to go!We gotta get the kids
这房子根本不是人呆的地方！
and we gotta get out of the house!
不，跟这房子没关系，你懂的
No, it's not the house.You know that.
我上次说过了
We've been through this before.
是里关那只鬼，他们会跟过来的，你稍安勿躁
They will follow us You have to just not be afraid.
你得冷静下来
You have to relax.
冷静？你叫我怎么冷静！！
Relax? I can't relax!
到处都闹鬼！
There's ghosts everywhere!
我感觉我们都已经死了，就像在地狱！
It's like we're already dead!
不，不是的！
No, it's not!
没人死
No, it's not.
谁都没死
This is nothing like being dead.
我清楚，我见过鬼魂
I know.I have seen it.
我在那个世界见过它们
I have seen where these things exist.
它们想要的是
They want what you have.
寄生
Life.
但是它们斗不过你
But they have no power over you.
阻止它们的办法就是：无视一切，随他们自生自灭
All you have to do is ignore them, and they will go away.
我就说它会自己弹
See, I told you.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
它刚才弹的是这首曲子
That's the song that's been playing.
什么曲子？你在说什么？
What song?What are you talking about?
你不知道这曲子吗？
You don't know that song?
是的，我不知道
No, I don't.
这曲子是我写的，是我为你写的
That's my song,the song I wrote for you?
我们该关心的不是钢琴曲
Well, it's not the song that we should be worried about.
是那些不速之客
There's somebody in this house.
呆那别动
Stay here.
瞧瞧，人都死了窗户还开着
Hey, look,they left the window open.
小心脚下
Watch your step.
有情况吗？
Do you feel something?
恩。。
Um..
我只能说这地方
Let's just say that this house is not a place
發生了許多"好事"
where many good things have happened.
说不定藏了什麼好東西呢
Probably a lot of good collectibles in here.
这什么味道？
What is that smell?
斯佩克斯
Hey, Specs.
在
Yeah.
上楼
Upstairs.
我猜这应该是他的卧室吧
I'm guessing this might be Parker Crane's bedroom.
看上去怎么更像女孩子的闺房
No, it seems a little girly for a boy's bedroom'
不觉得吗？
don't you think?
啥？
Why?
我是説，你看看這個娃娃屋
I mean, look at this dollhouse.
什么？
What?
我也有套娃娃屋
I had a dollhouse.
这是罗德岛红鸡
This is a Rhode Island Red.
好了，我们离开这
Come on, let's get outta here.
这是我的房间！
This is my room!
塔克
Tucker!
听，塔克，塔克
Listen,Tucker. Tucker.
你们不能在这
You can't be in here.
让她看见的话，她会让我杀了你们
If she sees you,she'll make me kill you.
道爾頓
Dalton.
什么事？
What?
我要给你看一出好戏~~
I have something to show you.
不要闹了，福斯特
Stop, Foster.
赶紧睡觉，别找麻烦
Just go back to bed. You're gonna get us in trouble.
我，不是，福斯特~~
I'm not Foster.
福斯特，醒醒！
Foster, wake up.
福斯特！醒醒！
Foster, please wake up!
你是谁？
Who are you?
被他杀掉的人其中一个
The ones he killed.
我们都被他杀了
We are many.
你要干嘛？
What do you want?
请救救我
Please help me!
我再也受不了！
Make the pain stop!
没事没事，妈妈在这，别怕别怕
It's okay! It's okay! It's okay!
好了好了，别怕宝贝
It's okay!It's okay! It's okay!
天呐！哦，天呐！
Oh, Jesus.Jesus. Oh, Jesus.
没事了，没事了
It's okay.It's okay. It's okay.
是梦，只是个梦
It was just a dream.It's just a dream.
只是个梦
It's just a dream.
你想联系她？没用的
You're trying to reach her, but you won't.
别再挣扎了
Not from over there.
好好当你的鬼吧
Shadows are your home now.
救命！
Help!
伊莉丝
Elise.
为什么引领我们到这来？
Why did you bring us here?
我们需要找到什么？
What are we looking for?
"MORS"?
拉丁文里面是指死亡？
Latin for "Death"?
卡尔
Carl.
这个女人就是出现在我家的怪人
This is the woman who was in my house.
罗琳！当心！
Lorraine, lookout!
出什么事了？
What happened?
-怎么会这样？
-這邊來一點光
-What happened?
-Give me a light over here.
对准这里！
Over here!
你根本不是伊莉丝！对不对！
You're not Elise, are you?
“对”
你是谁！
Who are you?
“MATER MORTIS”
死人的母亲？
Mother of Death.
啥玩意儿？
What does that mean?
这是字面意思
It's literal.
其实是说一直给我们信息的
It simply means the mother
是帕克·柯蓝的母亲
of Parker Crane.
好，使劲
Okay, move that.
一，二，三
One, two, and three.
推过去
Pull it this way.
别碰任何东西
Don't touch anything.
伙计们
Guys.
“黑寡妇”
"Bride in Black."
我见过这个名字。。。
I know that name.
在哪？发现什么了？
Where? What you got?
“其中一个受害者侥幸逃出变态的魔窟”
"One of the victims managed to elude the killer.
“受害者向警方描述变态的样貌”
"Police said she described her attacker
“像是一个老女人穿着黑色的婚纱和面罩”
"as an old woman dressed in a black wedding gown and veil."
黑寡妇杀了15个人
Bride in Black claims his 15th victim.
15个。。。
Victims.
哦我的天
Oh my god
等等
Wait a sec.
额
Uh..
帕克就是黑寡妇！
Parker wore that dress
他绑架残杀受害者
to commit these murders.
他是个變装癖
It was his disguise.
是他母亲逼他杀人
He killed for his mother because she forced him to.
他想要回他的童年
He wanted his childhood back.
所以他看中了你儿子
That's why he went after your son.
-蕾纳依
-天呐，妈？！
-Renai!
-Jesus! Lorraine!
你上哪去了？
Where have you been?
听我说
I need to speak to you.
賈許，他在哪？
Where is he, Josh?
他身体感觉不太好，一整天都躺床上
He's not feeling well.He's been in bed all day.
道爾頓和福斯特呢？
And where are Dalton and Foster?
我刚从杰西卡那接他们回来
I just dropped them off at Jessica's.
-你怎么了？
-你和孩子们很危险
-Why?
-You and the kids are in danger.
我会解释的，先上车
I'll explain, but not here.
快，快上车我们走
Please, let's just get in the car and go.
你是不是也看到了？
Have you been seeing them, too?
房子里的鬼魂？
Around the house?
跟房子无关，是賈許
It's not the house, it's Josh.
-她们走了
-开始行动
-They're gone.
-It's go time.
安上这个，我们就能听到了
Okay.We'll hear everything.
需要我们的时候就大叫
Sing out if you need us.
暗号是“墨西哥饼”
The code word is "Quesadilla."
-跟我念一遍，墨西哥饼
-墨西哥饼
-Say it with me. Quesadilla.
-Quesadilla.
等一下，暗号不是说好用“独角神兽”的吗？
I thought we agreed on "Unicorn" as the code word.
额，相对来说“墨西哥饼”更顺口
Uh.. "Quesadilla" is easier to bring up in conversation.
一点不顺口，你平常跟人讲话
Not at all.How would you bring up
会提到墨西哥饼吗？
"quesadilla" in a conversation?
-午饭时间了，吃墨西哥饼吧
-我说你们二位，二位
-It's lunch time. It's quesadilla time
-Guys, guys
-我想吃墨西哥饼，可以给我来一块吗？
-二位，二位
-I'd love a quesadilla.Can I have a quesadilla?
--Guys, guys
说真的
Really
用哪个暗号并不重要
I don't think it matters.
我需要帮助时你们会知道的，不用什么暗号
You'll know if I need you.It doesn't matter.
这是麻醉剂
Tranquilizer.
給賈許：我带蕾纳依去逛街了，回头见
妈
有事吗？
Can I help you?
我叫卡尔
My name's Carl.
额。。我知道你一定不认识我了，賈許
Uh, I know you don't remember me, Josh.
伊莉丝和我竭尽全力帮你忘记那件事
Elise and I did our best to make sure of that.
你说的没错，我确实不认识你
You're right,I don't remember you.
你小时候遇到一些麻烦，你妈曾委托我来处理
Your mother called me when you started experiencing some problems
我那时候有点害怕，事情没办好，于是我请来伊莉丝
and what I saw scared me so badly that I, uh, reached out to Elise.
如今伊莉丝去世了
Now Elise is gone.
我。。我想请你帮我来收个尾
I was wondering if you could help give me some closure.
帮帮忙
I need it.
当然可以
Sure.
谢谢
Okay.
呼~~~~
Phew!
真是有够刺激的！
This is pretty exciting.
咱可以当FBI了
I feel like an FBI agent.
妈，快告诉我到底怎么回事，你都知道些什么？
Tell me what you're thinking.Lorraine, what do you know?
我们一致认为：真正的賈許，还困在里关世界
I think that when Josh went into that other world,
某个恶灵附在他肉身上溜出来了
something else came back.
我们已查清楚，这个恶灵
We believe it's a spirit that's killed
生前杀了很多人，现在他还会继续作恶
many times before,and it'll kill again.
所以我才叫你赶快带孩子们跑路
That's why I had to get you and the kids away from him.
昨天晚上，我像过去12年每天那样
Last night, when I looked into his eyes,
注视着他的眼睛
like I have every day for the last 12 years,
我第一次感到他那么的陌生
was the first time I didn't recognize him.
他嚇壞我了
I was scared of him.
现在有个灵媒师正在家中
Right now, at the house,
他是我和伊莉丝当年的朋友，他正在和賈許谈话
there is an acquaintance of Elise's and mine, and he's talking to Josh.
我们计划驱逐恶灵
We're going to try to sedate him and when he's under,
并救回真正的賈許
we're going to try to reach out to the real Josh.
可是万一失败了呢？
And what if we can't find him?
你身体还好吧？
Are you feeling okay?
我很好
I'm fine.
就醒来时感觉有点不舒服
Just woke up feeling a little under the weather.
我想问你的是
I suppose I wanted to ask you
关于伊莉丝的死，你有什么想法吗？
if you've any idea what happened to Elise.
不，我没想法
No, I don't.
额。。。我
Look, I..
我得提醒你的是，额。。。
I should remind you that, um..
我不是来看你笑話的
I'm not the person who's gonna look at you funny
我想听点不寻常的事
if you tell me something unusual.
恩恩
Mmm-hmm.
我亲眼目睹过很多人
I've seen things with my own eyes
睡着后能看见自己躺在床上
that most people have to go to sleep to conjure up.
伊莉丝将我送进那个到现在仍令我做噩梦的鬼地方
Elise sent me to a place that still haunts my dreams.
可我救回了我的儿子
But I got my son back.
我不清楚，我离开那房间大概10分钟
I don't know, I left the room for about 10 minutes
等我回来时，伊莉丝已经死了
and when I came back Elise was dead.
是被人掐死的
She had been strangled.
这可真令人毛骨悚然
That's pretty horrific.
我想起来。
I guess.
噢！
Oh!
额。。。
Um..
你小的时候
When you were a boy,
说有个老妇经常骚扰你
you said it was an old woman who haunted you.
那么在你进入里关世界后
Did you see that same old woman?
有没有碰见那个老妇？
When you were in that other world?
没有
No.
好吧
Okay. Um..
对了，想喝点什么？
Say, would you like a drink?
额。。。额。。。水，一杯水就行了，谢谢
Water. A glass of water would be nice.
好了
Sure.
你在那找什么呢？
What you got there?
啊？哦！额。。
Huh? Oh. Uh..
没什么
Nothing.
你是不是在玩你的骰子
I thought maybe you were playing with your dice.
什么？
Excuse me?
我妈说你喜欢掷骰子
Mother tells me you like to play with dice.
是吗？你们早上还聊到我了？
Did She? I didn't realize you guys had spoken this morning.
这我用来算卦的
It's how I do my readings.
啊
Ah.
你背后藏着什么？
What have you got behind your back?
你骰子投出什么，我背后就藏着什么
Why don't you ask your dice what I have behind my back?
来吧，投子问天
Come on, roll them and see.
我妈说你这招那是相当的灵验
Mother tells me you were very good with them at the house.
投吧，很有意思
Come on, it'll be fun.
好吧
What..
賈許背后。。
What does Josh..
应该是帕克·柯蓝背后藏着什么？
What is Parker Crane holding behind his back?
“刀”
她永远都是对的！
She was always right.
該死！
Shit!
啊！
Ah!
快啊！
Come on!
墨西哥饼！
Quesadilla.
- 卡尔！
- 在这！
- Carl!
- In here!
抓住了！
I got you!
我认得你，是吗？
I know you, don’t I?
既然能见到你，我想我不用再问这是哪了
Well, if you're here, I guess I don't have to ask where I am.
他杀了你
He killed you.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我若再不回去，我的家人一定会被这畜生杀害的
That thing is gonna murder my family if I don't get back.
可我被困在这，而且感觉离开肉身后
I am trapped here.I'm getting weaker
灵魂日渐虚弱
the longer I'm away from my body.
伊莉丝呢？
Elise.
伊莉丝？她不在这
Elise, she's not here.
那我们就得找到她
Well, then we'll have to find her.
继续深入搜索
Into the Further we go.
你一定要杀了她们
You need to kill the others.
这是你唯一的生存机会
It's the only way to stay alive.
闭嘴！闭嘴！滚出我的脑子！
Shut up! Shut up!Get out of my head!
闭嘴！你滚！给我滚！
Shut up!Get outta here!
滚得远远的！
Get out of my head!
我刚收到塔克的微信，他说一切准备就绪
Okay, I've just got a message from Tucker He says they're ready.
伊莉丝？
Elise?
伊莉丝！
Elise!
别這樣做
Don't do that.
怎么了
What is it?
你前方站着个人
There's someone standing in front of you.
我没看见有人啊
I don't see anybody.
他就在你面前
He's right in front of you!
他在。。
He's..
他在跟你讲话
He's talking to you.
他說了什麼？
What's he saying?
他要你的孩子
"He's got your baby. "
他要你的孩子，他要你的孩子，他要你的孩子
"He's got your baby. He's got your baby.He's got your baby. "
他要你的孩子，他要你的孩子
He's got your baby.He's got your baby.
现在呢？他在做什么？
What's he doing now?
他好像。。。
He..
在给我们指路
He's pointing at something.
那边
Over there.
凯丽房间里有怪声，从婴儿监控器传来的
I heard this noise coming from Kali's room.It was on the baby monitor.
可能是电波串线收到别的信号
Probably just inteference.
不知道
I don't know.
可听起来很清楚，像是谁在窃窃私语
It sounded so clear. It was like this whispering. It was..
吓死我了
Scared the hell out of me.
然后我去挺监控器，加大音量
Then I went to hear the monitor and turned up the volume
听到一个男人的声音
and heard a man's voice.
不！不！不！
No! No! No.
不！嘿！
No! Hey!
什么声音？
Who the hell is that'?
等等
Hold on.
你留在这
Stay here.
蕾纳依！！
Renai!
有人吗？
Hello?
賈許！不要！
No, Josh, no!
賈許！賈許！快啊！这有人！ 有人在窗帘里！
Josh! Josh! Quick! There's someone in here!Someone in the curtains!
賈許！賈許！
Josh! Josh!
蕾纳依！
Renai!
别动她！
Get away from her!
离她远点！
统统退散！
Go to hell!
賈許
Josh.
我想我应该说：见到你真高兴
I wish I could say it's good to see you.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你不该在这
You shouldn't be here.
我们最终还是在这栋房子相遇了
We all pass through this place eventually.
希望早日离开这里，去个好点的地方
Hopefully, on our way to someplace better.
我已经去过美妙的地方了
I've seen that better place
可是我又回到这里，因为我听到了你的召唤
but I came back here because I heard you calling
我想我能够帮你
and I think I can help.
卡尔，你怎么来了？
Carl, what are you doing here?
你不应该在这啊！
You are not supposed to be here
我感受到你了，伊莉丝
I felt you, Elise.
哦。。
Oh..
不，不是，你不是找我
No, you didn't.No, you didn't
你是想找賈許才找到这里的
You were looking for Josh and you found him.
賈許，你不属于这里
Josh, you don't belong here,
你属于表关世界！
and neither does that entity belong in your world
我不知道怎么跟她斗
I don’t know how to fight her.
在黑暗的那一边
Out there in the darkness,
有个房间，密存着她一生的记忆
she has a home where all her memories live from her life.
利用那些记忆把她驱赶出你的肉身
Use those memories to draw her out of your vessel
这样你才能回到表关世界
so that you can get back into your body
可我怎么才能找到那地方呢
But where do I find her home?
只有你知道地点
Only you know where that is.
我不记得了
I don't remember.
那我们就去问问那个中招的賈許
Maybe we're asking the wrong Josh.
怎么了
What happened?
我看到那家伙了，它绝非善类
I saw what haunts him,and ifs not a friend.
是一种寄生灵
It's a parasite.
我职业生涯从未碰到过此等恶灵
I've never felt such a malignant presence.
它想附体在賈許身上
It wants to be him.
兰伯特太太，我认为令郎拥有特殊的能力，一种天赋
Miss Lambert, I think your son has a unique ability, a gift.
賈許
Josh.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
关于那个老妇的记忆我全忘了
I don 'I have any memories of the old woman anymore,
但是你还记得
but you do.
我想知道她住在哪
I need to know where she lives.
我带你去
I’ll show you
原来是这么回事
So that's what that was about.
卡尔
Carl?
賈許
Josh?
嗨，亲爱的
Hi, honey.
我在等孩子们，还没回家
I'm waiting for the boys.They're not home yet.
今天我朋友卡尔没来过吗？
Did my friend Carl stop by today?
没来
No, I don't think so.
你们这是自寻死路！
You did this to yourselves!
呵呵，好久没这么疼过了
It's been so long since I felt real pain.
蕾纳依，快来帮我
Renai, help me!
我忘了疼痛，但这不代表我忘记怎么让别人疼痛
I missed it, but not as much as I miss inflicting it on others.
蕾纳依，快离开这，快跑！
Renai, get out of here! Run!
一会再来收拾你，妈咪！
I'll come back for you, Mommy!
- 到了，孩子们
- 耶！
- Okay, guys, we're here.
- Yay!
谢谢你，杰西卡
Thanks, Jessica.
-谢谢
-不用谢，明天见
-Thank you.
-No problem.See you tomorrow.
走吧，福斯特
Let's go, Foster.
我不想这样的，蕾纳依
I didn't want this, Renai.
她叫我杀了你们，我拒绝了
She wanted me to kill you, but I said no.
不过现在，我知道她说的是对的
But now, I know she was right.
你是个卑鄙无耻，忘恩负义的婊子！
You are a miserable,ungrateful bitch.
你这一天到晚胡思乱想的，简直是浪费生命！
You have no idea how much you've wasted
你不是怕周围都是鬼魂么？
your life being afraid of the dead,
现在好了，马上你自己也成鬼魂了
because pretty soon, you're going to be one of them.
然后，我把你带到我的小黑屋
Then, when I take you to my home in the dark,
你就会醒悟到你这婊子短暂的一生
you'll realize how happy you should've been
最快乐的时光就是在被杀的那一刻！
for your brief,little moment in the sun.
妈妈！妈妈！
Mommy! Mommy!
爸爸！不要！
Daddy! No!
快跑！
Come on!
你好
Hello?
我的名字叫帕克！
My name is Parker!
这是什么？
What is this?
是你写的吗？
Did you do this?
你好大的胆子！
Don't you dare!
但是，妈妈。。。
But, Mommy..
说实话
Speak the truth.
是你写的吗？
Did you?
-恩
-这不是你的名字！！！
-Yes.
-That is not your name!
帕克不是你的名字！！！
Parker is not your name!
那是你爹取的名字
That is the name your father gave you!
你的名字
Your name
是玛丽莲
is Marilyn.
你听清楚了吗？
Do you understand?
跟着妈妈说一次
Repeat after me.
我的名字叫玛丽莲
“My name is Marilyn. "
快说！！！
Say it!
我的名字叫。。。
My name is..
玛丽莲
Marilyn.
乖孩子
Quiet, now.
不做乖女孩，你就会。。。。
If you don't be a good little girl, you'll get..
妈妈！妈妈！我可以沉睡，然后去那个黑地方
Mommy, Mommy, I can go into the dark place
找爸爸来救我们！
and find Daddy,if I go to sleep.
不不，这太危险了！
No, it's too dangerous.
你上次差点醒不过来
I nearly lost you once before.
妈妈不能再失去你了
I'm not gonna let that happen again.
我一定能找到爸爸，我保证我们会回来的，我保证
I can find him. I promise I'll find him.I promise.
一定会的
I will.
后退
Turn around.
没事的
It's okay!
小心
Be careful.
我爱你
I love you.
搞掉她，賈許！结束这一切！
Destroy her, Josh!End this!
我在哪？
Where am I?
放开她！
Let her go!
罗琳？
Lorraine?
他在哪？
Where is he?
他在下面
He's got Renai.
可恶！
What the hell!
帕克，我来消除她对你的记忆，你要帮我
Parker, help me destroy the memories of her.
这样你就解脱了
It will set you free.
求你让我进去吧
Please let me in.
打开心门！
Open the door.
我的小女兒必須變得更好!
Little girls need to learn to be good!
不要啊~~~~~~~~~
No!
宝贝
Baby!
嘿
Hey!
嘿，回来啊，回来啊
Hey, come back!Come back!
伊莉丝
Elise!
賈許，快走！
Josh, go now.
真希望我可以帶你一起回去
I wish I could take you with me.
我走不了，但你可以帶上卡尔
I can't.But you can take Carl.
什么？
What?
我说过你不属于这里
I told you,you don't belong here.
我和你拥抱时我听得到你的心跳声
I felt your heartbeat when I hugged you.
你还活着，是时候该回表关世界了
You're still alive.It's time to live again.
你们两个快走
But you both have to go now!
快离开这！
Go now!
快啊
Go!
离开！
Get away
回去！回去！
Get back! Get back!
爸爸！
Daddy!
道爾頓？
Dalton?
道爾頓！
Dalton!
爸爸！
Daddy!
儿子你在哪?
Where are you, son?
爸爸！
Daddy!
哦！
Oh!
我的乖宝贝！你怎么会在这？
Oh, good bay!What are you doing here?
我来带你回家
I came to bring you home!
你怎么找到我的？
How did you find me?
我跟着你的脚步声
I followed your steps.
儿子快醒醒！
Please wake up!
你在哪？快回来吧！
Where are you?Come back, come on!
回到妈妈身边
Come back to me.
是妈妈
That's Mommy.
快醒过来
Wake up!
回到妈妈身边
Get back to me!
-聰明的小伙子
-跟我来
Clever boy.Follow me.
醒醒
Wake up.
快醒醒！
Come on, wake up!
是我
It's me.
宝贝，是我，没事了
Renai, it's me, it's okay.
都结束了
It's okay.
爸爸？
Daddy?
是的
Yeah.
爸爸，你回来了！
Daddy, you're back!
对！
Yeah.
谢谢你
Thanks to you.
我的好儿子，嘿，宝贝
My boys. Hey, buddy.
蕾纳依，是我，我回来了
Renai, it's me, it's okay.
我努力联系你，想尽一切办法
I tried reaching you I tried everything.
我还弹了那首曲子
I played your song.
我早该想到那是你
I should've known it was you.
只有你才会弹得那么烂
Only you could play it that badly.
放马过来！
Bring in
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
好了
We're ready.
准备忘掉那种能力
Ready to forget once and for all.
不想再回到那个世界了，对吧
No more traveling, right?
我们只属于这个世界
This is the only world we wanna be in.
很好，兰伯特先生
Good, Mr. Lambert.
那么，闭上眼睛
So then, close your eyes.
小兰伯特先生也是
Both of you.
做个深呼吸
Now take a deep breath,
听着摆针的声音
and just listen to the ticking.
你们感到很疲倦，很想入睡
Now feel yourselves getting sleepier and sleepier,
让那黑暗离你们越来越远
and let the darkness drift further
消失不见
and further away.
-谁啊？
-我来带个口信
-Who is it?
-I have a message for you.
是关于艾丽森的
It's about Allison.
你们搞啥名堂？
Is this some kind of joke?
我们有一个好朋友，她。。
We have a close personal friend who has, uh,
她和艾丽森談過了
spoken with Allison.
那不可能
That's not possible.
你们走吧，不然我报警了
You better leave now or I'm calling the police.
等一下，布莱恩
Wait, Brian.
请问你们是什么人？
Who are you guys?
我们以助人为乐，太太
Uh.. We help people, ma'am.
-我们帮助那些受困扰的。。。。
-那位女士是谁？
-People who've been afflicted by..
-Who's the lady?
宝贝，哪位女士？
What lady, honey?
站他们后面那位
The lady standing behind them.
嘘。。
Um..
我们的这位朋友让我们转达：
Our friend told us to tell you
艾丽森的意外其实并不是意外
that Allison's accident was no accident.
当她在医院复苏时
When she was resuscitated back to life at the hospital,
有灵魂跟着她回到了这里
she brought something back with her.
不只一个灵魂，有很多
Not just one thing, many things.
它们和你们一块住在这房间里
And they're living here in this house with you.
艾丽森
Allison.
我的天啊。。。
Oh, my God!
《潜伏2》全片完
====百度悬疑片吧字幕组====
水浒三国金刚  非晓生  AS小笼包
谢谢观赏